Are you two
really dating?
I'm asking
if it's serious
Did I ask something
too obvious?
Okay then, I'm asking you
because you're
in a relationship
with our leading actor
Do you have plans
for the future?
First of all, I'm gonna
leave the company
Well, this time
I'm asking you
as the president of JY
What do you think
of our agency?
[President
Lim Jeong-yeon]
I'm not just
feeling you out
We're extending
the business next year
scouting some
new actors
Don't take it
too seriously
Think about it
and call me later
Ah
Merry Christmas
Excuse me
I don't usually do this…
Me?
If you don't mind
can I have your number?
- Ah, my number…
- Honey!
What's taking so long?
Oh, I'm sorry
Have a good time
What are you doing?
I shouldn't
leave you alone
Hey, what are you saying?
Let's go to my place